<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Shofa Jannah</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Shofa Jannah</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 14:13:48 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Cognitive Systems: The Brainy Tech Behind Smart Decisions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/cognitivesystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 14:13:48 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/cognitivesystem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hello, hello&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wondered how Netflix seems to know what movie you’d love to watch next? Or how Google magically finishes your sentences before you even type them? That’s the magic of cognitive systems—a blend of artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning, and human-like reasoning that helps technology think, learn, and make decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Are Cognitive Systems?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine if computers could think like humans—analyze, understand, and even adapt to new situations. That’s what cognitive systems do! They mimic human cognition by processing information, recognizing patterns, and making intelligent decisions. Unlike traditional rule-based systems, cognitive systems continuously improve by learning from new data.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Magic of Computer Vision</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/computervision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 14:34:06 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/computervision/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Imagine a world where machines can see and interpret the visual wonders around us, just like humans do. That&amp;rsquo;s the enchanting realm of Computer Vision! It&amp;rsquo;s a fascinating field of artificial intelligence that enables computers to understand and process visual information from the world. Let&amp;rsquo;s embark on a joyful journey to explore this captivating technology.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Computer Vision?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At its core, computer vision is all about teaching machines to &amp;ldquo;see.&amp;rdquo; It involves enabling computers to interpret and make decisions based on visual inputs like images and videos. This technology mimics human vision, allowing machines to recognize objects, analyze scenes, and even detect anomalies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestine &amp; Israel Are Not a Religious Conflict</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/palestine-and-israel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 10:58:24 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/palestine-and-israel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hello, hello [Music]&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Assalamualaikum warahmatullahi wabarakatuh - peace be upon you and God&amp;rsquo;s blessings and mercy. I intentionally start with a greeting, as this content is not propaganda or any agenda an attempt to achieve anything else. This content is about peace, which can be felt by anyone who reads, even though the subject is the turmoil in Palestine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The tragedy of Palestine has once again resurfaced and is affecting this country and various countries around the world, sparking various frustrations and demonstrations from people of all religions and communities, from Europe, Asia, Africa, to America. I intentionally refer to what is happening there as the &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;tragedy of Palestine&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; because that is the root of the problem. And that is the reality there, something simple.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
